[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "Even today some Russian people refuse to ____ Stalin with the terrible crimes that were committed when he was Russian leader.", "Opt_1": "form", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The internet allows people to ____ whatever they want without needing to go to the shops.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The technology to ____ carbon monoxide into liquid fuel has been around a long time.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ student at our school spends about 90 minutes doing homework every evening.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to communicate in a way ____ words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most people have a ____ notion of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "optional", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The contributors assert that teaching is a gendered occupation with low ____ and relatively low pay.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally ____ bodies undergo multiple, concurrent, dynamic frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There will be a ____ class after school today for those who want extra practice for the test.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They all use tools from well outside the natural ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The researchers found that some of the key ____ makers lacked the proper knowledge and expertise to handle the disaster.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "One ____ was political: because we had decided to confine the project at first to the six northernmost counties in our region.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Participants will gain in-depth exposure to each ____ through classroom assignments and structured exercises within team environments.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We had to make sure that our customers in China knew that what we were doing was not an attack on Chinese industry, but a dispute over a ____ issue.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The School of Medicine will ____ the buildings in two phases.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This phenomenon is not rare: 99 percent of patients ____ a phantom pain after an amputation.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Testing personnel will not ____ any tester who is cheating, but will complete the Testing Incident Report and submit to the supervisor.", "Opt_1": "provide", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to give", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He has lost the ____ to consider what is right and wrong because he was hurt, indeed devastated, when the love of his life disappeared.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Studies have proven that taste is only a minor consideration in the ____ decision for soft drinks.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Parents who are alcoholics often ____ their children both physically. and emotionally.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The only ____ of having computers in the classroom is that they are loud and make the room hot.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A large ____ map shows a small area with a large amount of detail.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The conclusion did not distort the ____ of the situation even though the student distorted some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Recent research has investigated the traits that may ____ the development of drug addiction.", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The developing world does not create many industrial wastes; thus it has had little ____ to develop proper disposal techniques.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many schools in poorer parts of the world do not have ____ books and computers to give their students a good education.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It was an ____ thing he noticed when playing around with his new invention.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will find reference books on this shelf and the ____ ones.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The house was built so carelessly that it began to fall ____ after only a couple of years.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Richards understood the importance of her position, the image that she projected and the need to ____ her papers and records at the Center.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Advertising marketed directly to the consumer may minimize the risks and ____ the benefits of medications.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "cancel", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to cut or stop from happening"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Follow these recommended times for storage in the freezer to enjoy the best quality in flavor and texture and to ____ good nutritive value.", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Stephen Krashen, a distinguished scholar and leading ____ in the field of language acquisition, held an open forum to present his findings on five topics.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Any student who is at least 13 years old on September 30 is eligible to ____ the mathematics competition.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "To develop a comprehensive approach to business, managers must ____ the strengths of their employees in assigning tasks.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is ____ important to remember that parents as a group have not usually taken the riding lessons and are not competent to supervise their children.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The teacher gave us ____ instructions not to leave our seats while she was out of the room.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There has been no ____ statement about the number of soldiers who were killed in the fighting.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She didn't study for the vocabulary test, so ____ she got a low score.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "By studying these financial transactions, it is possible to ____ the amount of money that people are willing to pay for the essentials.", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You will receive a lengthy, very ____ email, which in short, states that your unsubscribe request did not succeed.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students must exhibit a working knowledge of a foreign language by translating a mathematical ____ into English.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "For the purposes of this study, then, increasing the testing strength did not yield more ____ results.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Could you please ____ this book to its proper place on the shelf.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some beach systems showed significant loss of sand in the ____ from 1964.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ answer is not at all straightforward, unless the uncertainty itself is related in a particular way to the passage of time.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has banned smoking in ____ all public places.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I do not wish to ____ that she is lazy, but her work is often late and of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In 2000, over seventy percent of India's population, and ____ three quarters of its poor, lived in rural areas.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The goals are to answer some of the most urgent questions to ____ significantly our scientific knowledge about Mars.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "About a quarter of the ____ and secondary students typically did not interact with the teacher at all during class.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small ____ was not sufficient to support early stage start-ups in the environment of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The aquarium owner decided sometime in the spring of 1992 to ____ the animal before any further damage or an accident with the other dolphins could occur.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "release", "Answer": "release", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to let go or let out"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The word 'gay' did not come to ____ 'homosexual' until quite recently.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "deny", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Learning lots of academic words will ____ your chances of success in school.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A doctor will usually ask her patient many questions in order to make a ____ of the illness.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The debate over whether North Korea will ____ and whether the United States should promote its ____ has paralyzed American policymaking.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "stipulate", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to require", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of most big cities around the main train station is often a dangerous place to be at night.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Traveling really gives students a better ____ of the world.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "target", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "aim, goal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government failed to ____ its goal of reducing unemployment among young people.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is much effort being expended on attempting to ____ this problem.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The German army planned to advance as far as Moscow, but were then stopped by the ____ Russian winter.", "Opt_1": "steady", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company's target for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to ____ this figure by 40%.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The group work done during these workshops will ____ in a series of papers, presented by project participants, at a one-day conference.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "encourage", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Among college students, concerns about body ____ and weight obsession remain widespread.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "stage", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most students are neutral about the suggestion to ____ the blackboards with whiteboards.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Thanks to the accurate description of the witnesses, the police were able to ____ the bank robbers.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is no place for those who have failed to ____ to better themselves with the opportunity afforded them.", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Force is not always the best ____ to get people to change their behaviour, and especially not their way of thinking.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You are making ____ progress in learning English.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Please ____ your answer to a maximum of 100 words.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The bulk of the urban districts, particularly in the Northern states, were totally ____ to this development.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many teachers are happier at a lower position in the school hierarchy. They do not want the ____ that comes with the top jobs.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Mr. Bush cannot answer Sheehan's question and he cannot justify the war of aggression ____ Iraq.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All new systems to the data center will need to undergo a security scan or audit ____ to installation.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I would be more prepared to ____ with the rules if I understood the reasons for them.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students needed to devote ____ time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The companies did not release the ____ results of the trial until almost two years after the trial was finished.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Coca-Cola is a drink that is ____ popular.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In order to ____ for the Olympic games 100-meter athletes need to have run under 10.2 seconds at least once this year.", "Opt_1": "suffer", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Educational websites have the ____ suffix: .edu. For example, the URL of this website is: esl.fis.edu.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "domain", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ambassador seems to have failed in his duty to correctly ____ the government he serves.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The data is ambiguous as some analysts measure this ____ according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school's decision to raise the tuition fees will have a serious ____ on the number of students who plan to attend.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She accepted the arduous task of vice president, according to the papers, saying that she could not ____ the will of the people.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "frustrate", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "To prevent this from happening, it is very helpful for patients to avoid talking unless ____ necessary for three days following surgery.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He did not ____ to develop a particularly good balance in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "adjust", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The student will have an opportunity to be re-examined if the initial ____ was not satisfactory.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I ____ the linguists, for not insisting that anyone who claims to be an educated person needs elementary competence in describing and analyzing the sound, form and meaning of human language.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The committee was tasked to review the tests and criteria used to determine ____ disability for purposes of eligibility for health Insurance benefits.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further ____ of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "instance", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "example", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Although his letter did not stipulate Atlanta as the ____ of the new school, the Educational Commission quickly decided the matter.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you talk through a cloth it will ____ the sound of your voice.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "view", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "sometimes", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If we learn to communicate effectively with others and are willing to ____ sharing our own feelings and respect other's feelings, many rewards will await us.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In some English reported speech sentences you can ____ the word that. For example, He said (that) he was sick.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "omit", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to leave something out or not do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Ours is the only generation that can prevent a massive ____ of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When faculty members assign an Incomplete grade they must ____ the work required.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "However, the Indian ____ is passing through a difficult phase in its history.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "His idea is simply not ____ - no one is going to pay that kind of money.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There was also no apparent record of an attempt to ____ the relationship between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "consent", "Opt_2": "accuse", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to agree", "Opt_2_def": "to blame", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Shonekan was unable to ____ Nigeria's ever-growing economic problems.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "For many persons these are not ____ concerns but profound and deep beliefs.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Do we have an ____ to help the poor?", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "route", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ____ answer.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will ____ an email from the Financial Aid office when your financial aid eligibility has been determined.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is scheduled to begin at 3:30 p.m. A decision to cancel or ____ the match will be made later in the day, if necessary.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The OCC provides counsel and ____ advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The business manager could not explain the ____ in the company's finances, and was asked to resign.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "sphere", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is located in the wooded ____ to the north west of Frankfurt.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more on the books that you read. It's not enough to just write what happens.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You should ____ a little more in class discussions. This will help to improve your spoken English.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you can't do your homework, you should ask your parents to ____ you.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As life spans increase, the fraction of life spent in retirement will rise unless we ____ our exit from paid work.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "delay", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Your report is good, but you need to ____ a paragraph on the causes of the accident.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government decided to increase its ____ to the countries of eastern Africa.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For most teachers the cash bonus was a nice acknowledgment of work well done, but not an ____ that influenced their behavior.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Nugent claimed that how technology is organized is ____ not a rational decision but rather one based on individuals and history.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The UK Highway ____ is the book of road rules that must be learned by new drivers.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "service", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The applicant's qualifications must ____ to the qualifications required to perform the duties of the position as indicated in the job description.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will ____ your chances of success if you are absent from school so often.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The purpose of this study was to explore the internal and external factors influencing the career development of first ____ Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The quality of your ideas and organization is much more important than the ____ of words you write.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more time to your studies and a little less time to your sports.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "High school students who have completed this difficult ____ deserve a reward.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the ____ to take if you decide to use email as an official means of communication.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Use this form when you need to ____ accidentally deleted files from the network.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "overcome", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to conquer, defeat"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The teacher had to ____ the boy from the rest of the class. His bad behaviour was disrupting their learning.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is especially true from an investing ____ when repeating the same strategy could be a road to utter disaster.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many of the world-wide organizations such as Greenpeace and Oxfam depend very heavily on ____ workers.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in ____ besides being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The rising price of oil could result in a global ____ disaster.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Since Ramadan emphasizes community aspects and since everyone eats dinner at the same time, Muslims often invite one another to ____ in the Ramadan evening.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "tend", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to often behave in a certain way"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Distance learning is the most significant ____ occurring in higher education today.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Certain items are not available at this time since the originals have been put into storage for the ____ of the construction.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The grant is not a sufficient ____ for the excellence and hard work of this faculty and staff.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The new version of Microsoft's Internet Explorer lets you ____ pictures by using the mouse ball and the Control key.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In August, UMBC will ____ a new home page on our Web site.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "sometimes", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The comprehensive and multidisciplinary International Lincoln Center for American Studies offers a year-round ____ of events to students and the community.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Use this ____ when you need to restore accidentally deleted files from the network.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The boss was right to ____ that his workers would return to work once it was clear that they would otherwise lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Do I have to be a member of the Society to ____ a paper?", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She came to school yesterday ____ feeling very unwell.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When we ask people to describe their characters when they are at their best, they ____ confident, hopeful, humorous, optimistic, resourceful.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of native-English speakers and non-native-English speakers at the school is about 40% : 60%.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Starting during the 18th century, attempts have been made to ____ the world's languages into one comprehensive genetic system of families.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a widespread belief ____ the public that the government lied about the reason for going to war.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You can ____ your work at any time prior to the due date.", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "submit", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If I make a ____ of England and Germany, I have to say I prefer Germany. The weather is better and the people are more friendly.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Committee is concerned that children dropping out of school during the compulsory stage of ____ have insufficient alternative ____al opportunities.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social ____ as a dumping ground for their spare cash, obsolete equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Entrants in this competition are challenged to use or ____ the building's unique infrastructure in the service of the people who learn and teach here.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "stipulate", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to require", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school needs to ____ the students' project work to the examination board before the end of the month.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you revise your work. This ____ that you make any necessary changes to its structure or content.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We did not ____ our selections on an author's nationality, religion, politics, or field of study; nor on an author's race or gender.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The latest trend ____ the girls in the school is to wear different colour socks.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government is thinking of extending ____ education by two years.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The findings directly ____ the assertion that some verbal areas of the brain are larger in women than in men.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Research strongly supports the ____ that publishing houses lack sufficient diversity in both high and middle-level staff members.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will need to explain your ____ as clearly as possible and provide appropriate supporting documentation.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government is unpopular and is expected to ____ badly in the forthcoming election.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government made the ____ decision to kill all cows in the area before the disease could spread.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you choose not to participate or to ____ from the study at any time, there will be no penalty.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The current program review process is not very ____ because there are neither rewards nor punishments for outcomes.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If a person tends to be ____ in relationships or at work, it is likely that her investment decisions will also be ____.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Not all patients with ____ disabilities need to stay in hospital.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The goal is to produce world-class scholars with capabilities in research, teaching, and service within the ____ area of Information and Decision Sciences.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We are often right on the ____ of warm and cold or moist and dry air masses. So we get some very difficult weather conditions to try to forecast.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The last ____ on earth to be explored was Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Although we did train the faculty in the revised teaching methods, in hindsight our training was not ____ enough to prepare them for the new course.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "forthcoming", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "coming soon", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school's ____ have been improved recently with the addition of a second library and media centre.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most famous footballers and film stars need an ____ to take care of their contracts.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Dmitrieva and Kuptsova adopt an identical ____ and understand culture as a realm of signs and meanings.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They were unable to ____ the distribution of food supplies because of the deteriorating security situation.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The profession of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and ____ of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "below"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The principle behind this policy is that the rights of the individuals should be respected; subjects must ____ to participation in research.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "tend", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to often behave in a certain way"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Military historians and other students of international security, gradually got into the habit of meeting together to ____ ideas.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government ____ did not take steps to investigate or punish the most serious cases of abuse.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Smith starts out with a ____ idea of what she wants to achieve.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will not be able to request a ____ name unless you provide the following information.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We had to make sure that our customers in China knew that what we were doing was not an attack on Chinese industry, but a ____ over a legitimate issue.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government is going to ____ a law that will prohibit smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "motivate", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If these reports are not returned, we will presume that you have used all ____ sick leave for that particular reporting period.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A popular type of TV programme shows people who escape the ____ world and pretend to live as farmers did 100 years ago.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The siting and design are a typical characteristic of ____ buildings that belong to a self-enclosed precinct.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students who seriously ____ network security or otherwise misuse the computing facilities will have their accounts terminated.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "During its congress, Committee failed to ____ even one woman to a leading position.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our teacher showed us an ____ of The Simpsons in ESL class yesterday.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "On-line learning applications will continue to multiply as educational institutions and. business corporations ____ new ways to expand their services.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "seek", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to look for or want"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some people ____ government elections every four years instead of every five as at present.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This unnecessary war will ____ the government plans to reduce tax.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To ____ an image on your website, you will need to insert the image into your webpage using an HTML editor.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "include", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These calculations are ____ to perform and are executed rapidly compared to Monte Carlo.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "FAQ > How do I ____ for free health services?", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In tomorrow's TV broadcast the government will declare its ____ to reduce taxes during its time in office.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A sound card is an essential ____ of a games computer.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The common, misinformed man did not ____ that fleas infected black rats, which in turn bit humans.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "realize", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "How to increase employment and reduce crime are the two most ____ problems that confront the new government.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is not the only method of teaching we use at the university; ____ we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most leadership training programs leave out the ____ question, namely how leaders actually affect their groups.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "People who move from the countryside to a large city often take time to ____ to urban living.", "Opt_1": "continue", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He has lost the ____ of being himself. Immigration laws have required him to pretend to be somebody else.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The teacher decided to ____ the activity when it became clear that the students didn't understand what to do.", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "suggest", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The beauty of the telephone, and something that the telegraph lacked, was that it required no ____ to operate.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many Western businesses are finding it difficult to ____ with Asian companies which pay their workers far less money.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "unite", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Board may ____ that those actions created a hostile or abusive work environment which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but ____ wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A new ____ of skin replaces the damaged skin during healing.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I don't think she realises the ____ of the task she has set herself.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The author had failed to ____ his report, so it was impossible to check the truth of his claims.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "shrink", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As migration is a spatial choice process, it is important to ____ how migrants perceive space and choose a destination in the space.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We hope to ____ the historic value of these buildings and encourage serious parties to step forward.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "By reason of the duress of mental disease, he has so far lost the ____ to choose between right and wrong.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If we accept your request to ____ the information, we will make reasonable efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the ____ment.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In 1986, 23 percent of parents said obedience was the most important ____ they expected from their children.", "Opt_1": "trait", "Opt_2": "issue", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_2_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "sometimes", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students worked in groups to ____ (or dis____) a series of mathematical statements.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Is the Smartboard just the latest teaching ____ that will be popular for a year or so and then disappear without trace?", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The main ____ of these wars is the social unrest, and the increasing economic and social divergence between the groups of the community.", "Opt_1": "committee", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Therefore, it is important to ____ low birth weight infants according to their weight for their gestational age.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I'm sorry but the school has no ability to educate children with ____ learning problems.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The illegal downloading of music via the internet is widespread ____ young people.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This certificate program is a ____ of fully online courses that will show you how to design and deliver a quality course via the Internet.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "status", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "position, standing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "San Francisco's justice ____ program is barely alive, says a UC Berkeley report.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "reform", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If your parents want to take you out of school during ____ time, they must have a legitimate reason.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This semester-long project begins with an overview in which students think about how to ask scientific questions and ____ hypotheses.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to ____ the cost of complying with new requirements regarding data recording.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As maintenance requirements and costs increase, fewer aircraft will be in a ____ state of readiness or mission-capable.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ is not a sufficient reward for the excellence and hard work of this faculty and staff.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In this paper we describe simple identification and signature schemes which enable any user to ____ his identity and the authenticity of his messages.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His beliefs were not ____ enough to withstand the influence of the people worked with.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In order to make up a missed exam, you must ____ written evidence within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a legitimate reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He told reporters that he did not want to intervene in the dispute over the ____ minister.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "While we were not ____ surprised by the answers to our questions, it was interesting to see the amount of uniformity in answers.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Director develops and oversees an ____ program of professional development and leadership training for history and social science teachers.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "ambitious", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some people have claimed that the sole reason for the invasion of Iraq was to gain ____ of the oil fields.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government needs to make a more serious ____ to ensure that all school-leavers have a job.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The relationship between Christianity and the Enlightenment remains a ____ issue in the history of Western civilization.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The museum plans to ____ a collection of late works by Picasso.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Scientists are working very hard to find a ____ for oil. They hope that one day cars will not pollute the atmosphere.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most serious kind of ____ is war. Many people die when countries have problems that cannot be solved in peaceful ways.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to focus not only on the skills and knowledge ____ to the high stakes tests but also the skills and knowledge to perform more authentic tasks.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you can ____ the problems you had with your last history project, I will be able to help you better with your current one.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "At the end of the lesson please put the ____ back in the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Please remember to ____ any rented vehicle before driving it and note any scratches or other damage to the vehicle on the rental form.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The conclusion did not ____ the truth of the situation even though the student ____ed some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In an era of privatisation and market rule we are facing the fact that ____ments will have to ____ a bit more.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "govern", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "His problems are largely ____ to poor concentration in class.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Because of computer problems there will be a ____ in the announcement of the winner.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "delay", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It circles the theater so that you can ____ projectors at any spot on the dome, whereas before we were limited to placing them toward the back of the room.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school cannot ____ its teachers to give up smoking, but it can tell them not to smoke inside the building.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The US government is considering if it should ____ its army from Iraq.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It can take as much as a ____ or more of hard study in a foreign language to become as fluent as a native speaker of that language.", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most simply, the strength of a ____ is measured by determining how much energy is required to break the ____.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "surplus", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "All ____ parties must unite in their proposals to stamp out racism.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some people accuse the USA of starting the war in Iraq in order to ____ control of its oilfields.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "choice", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "decision, selection"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most people have a vague ____ of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many shops these days have ____ doors. They open as soon as you approach.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I ____ you to spend part of the summer vacation reading. This is an excellent way to improve your English.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "advance", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to go or move forward; to get better"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Program is designed to ____ researchers whose ISBM-supported work appears in the academic literature.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "observe", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to watch carefully"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She will ____ reduce her chances of success if she continues to drink so much.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Austen does not convince us that a woman with Jane's mind, integrity, emotional intensity could fall and ____ in love with such a dubious character.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The B grade had come to signify work that was ____ acceptable.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For some people God is an ____ that influences every aspect of their life.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "domain", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and ____ invisible to ships.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Game reasoning is simply moral reasoning that occurs in the context of competitive sports, and ____ elsewhere as well.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Those who could not transform, chose not to, or who were considered a threat to the ____ were imprisoned and eliminated.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In my school district it is emphasized that teachers must ____ instruction for students.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "At this stage of our research we were unable to find a ____ for accessing the actual decisions made in these cases.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They would not fill their barrels when the captain told them, but instead, ran the ____ that there would be water ahead.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There are ____ parts of the planet that have not yet been explored. These are all on the ocean floor.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The profession of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and ____ of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In general, when you paraphrase, you use about the same number of words to ____ the idea that the writer uses in the text.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He told the members that he quickly called for a car and telephoned the White House to set up an urgent meeting in order to ____ what he had just learned.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "fear", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to be concerned or frightened about"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Men and women of all ages benefit from a ____ amount of daily physical activity (for example: 30 minutes of brisk walking or 15 minutes of jogging).", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "To accurately determine mass balance, stakes were placed in the ____ clean ice areas of the glacier.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Tower of Hanoi is an ancient puzzle involving three pegs, and an ____ number of circular discs, each of a different size, and with holes in their centers.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The first section of this course is concerned with understanding the basic concepts of design: How to ____ and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you order a book from Amazon, you usually ____ it within a few days.", "Opt_1": "focus", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The main ____ of the school is the teaching of science and mathematics.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "sometimes", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Curiously absent from the report is any ____ of the type of action that the State would have taken against the diverse sources of TCE.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Insurance salesmen often ____ profits that they know are very unlikely.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "That doesn't mean I have a personality disorder because I conduct myself in a different ____ to different people.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She said she initially had planned to ____ earlier, but that she postponed her departure because of pressing issues at the hospital.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Then you will need to ____ the selection criteria you want to use.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Fire Chief Anthony Yenzer said the probable ____ of the fire was determined shortly afterwards through interviews with the two male students.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After an ____ period of introduction and practice, the German course begins with Chapter 1 in the text Deutsch: Na klar!", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He said that he did not want to discuss the issue until the ____ meeting.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Since the U.S. flu vaccine ____ was cut in half early this month, shots are scarce, lines long and some people are certain to miss out.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A small proportion of the government were ____ the Prime Minister's plan, but they were outvoted.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Nugent claimed that how technology is organized is generally not a ____ decision but rather one based on individuals and history.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "probable", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I assume his strange behaviour ____ is the result of his parents' divorce.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We reserve the right to refuse alcohol service to anyone who cannot provide ____ identification.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to ____ the reasons for your lack of success.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ to peace and prosperity in the region can only commence when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "With her departure we have decided to suspend teaching Spanish this fall as we await the ____ report.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The main ____ of the school is the teaching of science and mathematics.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The interpretation fits well with the fact that his ____ health did not deteriorate.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some animals, such as the tortoise or snail, have an ____ shell rather than an internal skeleton.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A classic ____ of learning vocabulary is to write words and their translations in a small notebook.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company made a ____ reduction in its workforce in order to improve its performance in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly cautious and to ____ yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Mrs. Cassells did not view us as young children in need of constant guidance, but ____ thought we should have the opportunity to make our own decisions.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you revise your work. This means that you make any necessary changes to its ____ or content.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Including future irrelevant costs ____ will not lead to a poor choice; it will only complicate the analysis.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "sometimes", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot ____ its ordinary meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "People are right to be suspicious of any diet that promises ____ success.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or ____ analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "outstanding", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "actual", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "excellent", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "real"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We need to regulate ____ to new lands made possible by road expansion.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is the ____ of every teacher to be prepared for class and to do everything he or she can to help the students learn.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It seems natural that we would want to employ nurses from overseas; after all we ____ everything else.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The topic of child deaths in the nineteenth century is one which could hardly fail to interest any ____ scholar of the period.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The New Investigator Competition is an award for the best paper by a graduate student, carrying with it a prize valued at ____ \ufffd\ufffd500.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A large ____ of the country is under water after the heavy rainfall of the last 2 weeks.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "portion", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Google uses a unique computer program to ____ its lists of hits within a very short period of time.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Computer hard disk cleaning is not an ____ that many people perform very frequently.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The entire collection is complete and ____ for online access.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Kennan had no ____ that the Soviets had regional, if not global, ambitions.", "Opt_1": "apparatus", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Furthermore, the text of the paragraph should correspond to the ____ sentence.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school's facilities have been improved ____ with the addition of a second library and media centre.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "too"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The last death occurred on Thursday morning when a deaf man apparently walking to work did not obey a police order to ____ and was shot.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many scientists are working hard to ____ a robot that can understand spoken language and do jobs around the house.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "create", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "create", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a familiar ____ of innovation to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He was unable to ____ the methods and texts advocated by these educators with the powerful ideas of the critical pedagogues shaping his opinions.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Doctors advise that the better way to get and stay healthy is to eat lots of fruit and vegetables and take ____ exercise.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You need to ____ the reasons for your lack of success.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Employees' levels of ____ motivation will decrease if they feel they are being controlled by their employers through extrinsic rewards.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While a ____ degree of agreement was attained, a uniform approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "random", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most people do not ____ politicians who make promises everyone knows cannot be kept.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "warn", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "\"I'll ____ you these 7 Pokemon cards for your 8 Yugioh cards.\"", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "exploit", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you accept a housing assignment in the Summer Allocation and subsequently cancel it or ____ to move in, you are charged an administrative fee.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "fail", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is important to ____ that the information noted on the sign-off form is correct and that all necessary signatures have been obtained.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When you employ an electrician to do a job in your house, you hope they will be ____ at their job.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You should expect ____ grading of all assignments.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The university has decided to ____ its modern languages department to meet the growing interest.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "cancel", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to cut or stop from happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The last ____ of the flooded village was evacuated by a helicopter.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you ____ the figures carefully, you will see some strong patterns.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The regime, which is bound to ____ under the deadweight of its own internal contradictions, is going to ____ on our heads.", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "accuse", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to blame", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Asian companies are good at building small cars but will never ____ the mainstream US car market.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A ____ method of learning vocabulary is to write words and their translations in a small notebook.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is an obvious ____ to her absences from school: Monday mornings and Friday afternoons!", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "profession", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "job; occupation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She found, however, that there is no documented process for achieving a ____ response to adversity.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I can survive on a ____ income. I don't need lots of money.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A common task in the English classroom is to ____ the parts of speech into nouns, adjectives, verbs, etc.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The outcome of the government's willingness to pay kidnappers to ____ hostages is that now there are more kidnappings and more hostages.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "release", "Answer": "release", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to let go or let out"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Rexhepi said the incident damaged the ____ for the upcoming talks on practical matters between Kosovar and Serbian officials.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a profound ____ on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She says she's not a very good pianist, but I know that the ____ is true and she's just being modest.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Unlike other animals, humans have no ____ for survival; we often choose to do things that may be detrimental to our health.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He is an American ____ which obviously puts him in a different category from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "sequence", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The comprehensive and multidisciplinary International Lincoln Center for American Studies offers a year-round ____ of events to students and the community.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to ____ a full application including: cover sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ behind this policy is that the rights of the individuals should be respected; subjects must consent to participation in research.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A concise and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too ____ or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "One ____ of the internet that concerns many parents and teachers is that a huge amount of very offensive material is just a click away.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a ____ request for extension of the project due date.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Each student must construct a Web ____ based upon his or her major research project.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "All campus party noise must ____ by 12:00 Midnight.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school have employed some guards to make the campus more ____ against unannounced visitors.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Each student's experience was so varied that I was unable to ____ common themes for discussion.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She will harm her chances of graduating unless she starts to ____ school more regularly.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "attend", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We all have to ____ differences of opinion in the political world and, in order to do that, we have to understand that there are real reasons for these differences.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Instead of getting involved in the affairs of other countries, the government should concentrate on its ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government clearly did not ____ carefully enough on the consequences of its new law.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government can ____ its message about the dangers of drinking if it increases the price of alcohol.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The headmaster called a meeting to try to ____ the dispute between the two teachers.", "Opt_1": "settle", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Individuals with communication disorders have ____ difficulty making themselves clearly understood.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The board was unable to ____ a candidate in the first round because of disagreement over candidates' performance.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The names of new products such as cars are not chosen at random. A large amount of research goes into choosing the most ____ name.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "enormous", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "very big", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company made a ____ reduction in its workforce in order to improve its performance in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Specifically, you ____ that you were not provided with academic adjustments and auxiliary aids, and were not provided access to other services and programs at the College.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you ____ the figures carefully, you will see some strong patterns.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a ____ to give someone the opportunity to pursue higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Is anyone in class ____ with the terms 'subject' and 'predicate'?", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "familiar", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has failed to ____ a willingness to listen to people's concerns.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "manifest", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ farmers who grow crops that can be used to run cars.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "fare", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of child deaths in the nineteenth century is one which could hardly fail to interest any serious scholar of the period.", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I don't know how I always ____ to get such a good grade. I never work particularly hard.", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Computers are a much more ____ way of storing and retrieving large amounts of data than keeping it on paper in huge cabinets.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is slightly down from the 19 percent failure ____ last year but still significantly above the failure ____ in other freshmen subjects.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The unexpected shortage of flu vaccine during winter 2004/2005 caused ____ concern.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It seems natural that we would want to employ nurses from overseas; after all we ____ everything else.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This article will only introduce the issues ____ than present a detailed analysis with proofs.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This project will ____ in a major research essay of 2000 words.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He was unable to ____ his plans for an industrial area, which he purchased from the Israel Land Administration.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "China is able to manufacture goods cheaply because ____ costs are low.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The World Bank said China has the capacity to ____ the impact of the recent international financial market fluctuations.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the precaution to take if you decide to use email as an ____ means of communication.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "against"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The police ____ found it difficult to explain why the wrong man had been arrested.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "random", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Ours is the only ____ that can prevent a massive loss of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You must ____ a bibliography to all reports that are based on information found in books or on the internet.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school has decided to ____ a ban on smoking anywhere on campus. This also applies to teachers.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Lebanese security officials said the soldiers' tank drove over a mine, but Israel said it could not ____ that.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There will be a ____ of Chinese art, literature, instruments, calligraphy, and fashion from noon to 4 p.m. on Wednesday, February 27.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "On hearing of the terrorist ____ the president called an immediate meeting of his top advisers.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Previous experience in such areas, especially microscopy, would be an ____ but is not essential.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Be sure to ____ and disinfect feeding equipment and other objects that may have come in contact with the sick animals.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The method of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will ____ include a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a comprehensive final exam.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is important to ____ that the information noted on the sign-off form is correct and that all necessary signatures have been obtained.", "Opt_1": "reject", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Standing on the table is certainly no way to ____ in the cafeteria!", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You must try to ____ a balance between work and play. At the moment it's too much play!", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "All the forms below can be electronically filled and submitted with the exception of Form B, which must ____ personal copies of material.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The last week of the tennis tournament will ____ the first week of the Olympic Games.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "overlap", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The illegal downloading of music via the internet is widespread ____ young people.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no need to ____ in detail the contributions of science to that war effort.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We should seriously ____ the idea of the internet elections, which are a totally feasible option.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Questioning the values of parents is ____ in being a teenager.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government needs to do more to ____ its success in fighting unemployment.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The new government plans to ____ the best possible health service for all of its citizens.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Strong families possess the ability to ____ both daily stressors and difficult life crises creatively and effectively.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Beethoven was not an ideal parent and enormous ____ developed between the two, contributing to his son's attempted suicide in 1826.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you can ____ your intelligence with hard work, you have a good chance of success.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was an extremely conservative institution, and did not ____ its business to any extent.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "allocate", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Nugent claimed that how technology is organized is generally not a ____ decision but rather one based on individuals and history.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She recognized the importance of introducing a plan that was ____ enough to meet the changing demands of the university.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government is planning to ____ all new mothers with a book advising them how to take care of their baby.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your ____ is to learn the English words that will help you be successful in your school subjects.", "Opt_1": "asset", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If we accept your request to amend the ____ation, we will make reasonable efforts to ____ others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "propose", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The computer manager is trying to ____ who has been sending email spam to all the teachers and students.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "My parents will ____ that I did this work without help.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Lack of sufficient ____ often prohibits sound management activities that are necessary to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You have made no ____ to learn, thus you will not be entered for the test.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An enormous amount of research has been conducted into the ____ by which young children learn to speak.", "Opt_1": "sphere", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The libraries are in a poor ____ and are in urgent need of restocking with new books and journals in both Arabic and English.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "state"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is especially true from an investing perspective when repeating the same strategy could be a road to ____ disaster.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I tried to ____ the information on the internet, but could find nothing useful.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The recent conference about green energy failed to ____ the interest of the British public.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is the completely ____ response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but nevertheless wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There's no need to give an ____ answer, Two or three short sentences will be enough.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to negotiate an extension with the TA ____ such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The workers did not ____ to lose their jobs. It was the managers who made the mistakes, not them.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "deserve", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is no ____ of an original idea in this essay.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Participants donate a small amount of blood or saliva, which will be used as a ____ to blood from children with genetic diseases.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Mr. Bush cannot answer Sheehan's question and he cannot justify the war of aggression ____ Iraq.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The contributors assert that teaching is a gendered occupation with low ____ and relatively low pay.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was a ____ move, but frankly we didn't have a choice.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The army sent 2,000 of its soldiers to ____ clothing to the refugees driven out of their homes by fighting.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is to be expected, of course, since natural selection is a natural process, and one cannot ____ moral principles from scientific findings.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This ____ text contains the typical method of trisecting a segment.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "After several years of work, the project team was not able to ____ the political support needed to maintain funding for the integrated service program.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is some ____ that she will turn in her work on time. She's not very reliable.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Trying to water-ski for the first time is difficult but if you keep practising, you will ____ learn how to do it.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The siting and design are a typical characteristic of ancient buildings that ____ to a self-enclosed precinct.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A student should declare a Literature ____ by the first semester of his or her junior year.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I believe that people often neglect the hardships the parents ____ if their child has a learning disability.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some historians still hesitate to ____ the incidents of 1915 as 'genocide ', choosing to use words like 'massacre ' or 'atrocities ' to describe the events instead.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government are concerned about the ____ small number of people who voted in the last election.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The German government should have realized that it would ____ matters by allowing the different German states to have their own regulations about smoking in public buildings.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Congress is resolved to ____ online gambling in America.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "alter", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "No matter how good the lawyer's intuition and ability to express himself or herself, the lawyer will not succeed unless he or she can ____ logically.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social sector as a dumping ground for their spare cash, ____ equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a ____ global society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Certain items are not available at this time since the originals have been put into storage for the ____ of the construction.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It takes a lot of ____ to cook a meal for 20 guests.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "result"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The results suggest that the best models will almost always ____ both vertical and horizontal processes.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief ____ for lunch, he stared at the history project which was due the next morning.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In recognition of your continuous ____ service to the university, you will receive an award at five-year intervals.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many new astronomy learners, students and adults alike, are unfamiliar with the universe ____ the solar system.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The teacher's threat to give the student a detention had an ____ impact on his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "One crucial reason for this persistent problem is that Europe is trailing behind the US in ____ productivity growth.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Because of their behavior in protecting food sources, it is ____ unusual to see two hummingbirds spending time together.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The teacher look like she was going to ____ angrily when I came late, but fortunately for me, she didn't!", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The new government proposals also ____ that all unemployed young people attend a three-week training course once a year.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "suggest", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you want your letter to be a private communication, I usually do not ____ sending copies to other people, since they may decide to act on the matter.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "determine", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Despite the ____ satisfaction that the program was predominantly successful, there are several ways in which the program could have been improved.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They are planning to ____ a new bridge behind the school.", "Opt_1": "construct", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to make", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ cause of the accident is that the driver fell asleep, but police are investigating the possibility of a terrorist attack.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most people are ____ of the problem of global warming, but not many are willing to change the way they live.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The publishing company brought a sample of its books to ____ to teachers.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Do you think I will pass the test? - It will ____ how hard you work from now until the day of the examination.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Mechanisms by which comfrey can ____ the liver are unclear, but the main injury appears to be destruction of small veins, leading to cirrhosis.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In sports events it is a good idea at the start of the game to ____ energy that you are going to need later.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The teacher spoke so fast that it was difficult to ____ all the information he was giving.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Euro has taken on a dimension far greater than its ____ substance.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "ancient", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "very old"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She claimed that the disproportionate number of non-native speakers in the survey did not ____ the results.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Despite the overall satisfaction that the program was ____ successful, there are several ways in which the program could have been improved.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We further believe that the general quality of student writing will not improve unless we as a department are ____ to state explicitly the standards we require.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "willing", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This review found that some guidelines and standards for reprocessing rigid laryngoscopes are incomplete, inadequate, and not ____ with one another.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "consistent", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Iowa State Theater group will ____ \"The Complete Works of William Shakespeare\" five times during the festival.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school made a mistake when buying new computers. They are not ____ with the printers we have.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The powerful hold that the empire of Egypt had on Palestine at this time would not have permitted the rise of a significant ____ such as Israel.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is impossible to ____ any Yuan play in its original style because the music is lost and its social context has changed.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Too much stress can trigger problems with ____ and physical health, particularly over a prolonged period of time.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Through the exhibit and its constant updating, people will be able to ____ new, thought- provoking works of art from around the globe.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Older people should have a ____ check-up at the doctors at least once a year.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She didn't study for the vocabulary test, so ____ she got a low score.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science ____ beyond the sports field.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The police ____ give details of whom they have arrested until they know that the person will be charged with a crime.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The different religious groups gradually came to ____ that none of them could hope to prevail over all the others.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "realize", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "realize", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Specifically, you ____ that you were not provided with academic adjustments and auxiliary aids, and were not provided access to other services and programs at the College.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You need to ____ your work a little more closely for silly spelling or punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The medical company decided to ____ production of its heart drug when it heard reports of the unexplained deaths of many people who had been taking it.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Leadership is not a ____ that many people have.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "New challenges, opportunities, and demands are necessary to ensure that creativity and motivation do not ____ away.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "release", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to let go or let out"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The boss took the ____ decision to close the factory for a week.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The management wanted to dismiss the incompetent employee but could find no-one better to ____ him.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many tourists to foreign countries buy a ____ book to help them speak a few words of the language.", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "His idea is simply not ____ - no one is going to pay that kind of money.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Entrants in this competition are challenged to use or ____ the building's unique infrastructure in the service of the people who learn and teach here.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Monroe is a well-known ____ of the mechanical theory of education, with its cult of standardization, intelligence tests, etc.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Next you need to ____ a search statement so you can conduct a database search.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The results on the tests are ____ to expectations.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Under the new programme, employees will continue to ____ the same amount of paid time off as they did in the old programme.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "With regret, we have had to cancel the upcoming program on \"The Nervous System\" ____ to an unavoidable change in schedules.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "before"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The new teacher has been away quite often this year. I ____ that she will not be given a permanent job at the school.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "speculate", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "tend", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to often behave in a certain way"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The numbers of overweight and obese children worldwide are expected to climb ____ by 2010.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This has been the province of scientists and engineers for many years and has only recently been considered a hot research ____ with real business potential.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "History is filled with examples of military leaders who have suffered at the mercy of climate conditions that they failed to ____ adequately.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Next year the school will ____ a policy of no smoking on campus for both teachers and students.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The comprehensive and multidisciplinary International Lincoln Center for American Studies offers a year-round ____ of events to students and the community.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was ____ poorly designed and therefore not worth considering.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has set a clear limit on how much pollution factories are allowed to release into the ____ every year.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many of the faculty and students we talked with wanted to remain ____ and asked that they not be listed by name in our report.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A sound card is an ____ component of a games computer.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Including future irrelevant costs ____ will not lead to a poor choice; it will only complicate the analysis.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Of the questions asked in this section of the survey, having an ____ privacy policy is one of the highest percentage of responses.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge base ____ the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is a particular privilege to welcome several San Francisco State University alumni who ____ all that we commemorate today.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You are recommended to ____ every significant detail about each of your customers.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Metals ____ when heated.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental justice are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when ____ involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "order", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company's ____ was to increase sales by 20%. Due to the high cost of oil in the past year, it was not successful.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Traditional social skills strategies (such as board games about friendships and appropriate classroom behavior) ____ to be too subtle for many children.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but ____ wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In Ancient Rome not every ____ had equal rights.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The management is considering removing the salesmen's ____ to use company cars at the weekend for private purposes.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students who take the class are expected to choose a ____ problem they would like to address and collaborate with each other in researching it.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The bulk of the ____ districts, particularly in the Northern states, were totally averse to this development.", "Opt_1": "spare", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "not needed", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The text should contain a concise ____ of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Modern computers can ____ the equivalent of many millions of pages of writing.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is especially true from an investing perspective when repeating the same strategy could be a road to ____ disaster.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This was not ____ of Serbia alone; the population felt similar frustration in other parts of Yugoslavia and in Eastern Europe.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most people have a ____ notion of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no mechanism in the master plan to ____ whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government's ____ of reducing teenage drinking by raising the price of alcopops has not been very effective.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students, ____ and faculty have a right to privacy and neither reporters nor the public should be allowed to disrupt classroom instruction.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We must hope that her heavy involvement in the school's sporting programme will not be to the ____ of her studies.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Large numbers of older adult students do not possess the ____ computer knowledge required to attain a job.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government plans to introduce an ____ for long-term unemployed people to start looking for work again.", "Opt_1": "trait", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Not all members of the Bush Administration have been telling the entire ____ about their dealing with Iraq.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You have not made a clear enough ____ between the causes and effects of the disaster.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not the government's ____ to supervise what people are doing when they are online.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for her poor test scores is that she didn't prepare herself well enough.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company was unable to sustain its recent good ____ figures.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Different newspapers will often have a different account of the same event - ____ newspapers from different parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Madrid attack was like the September 11 attack in that government agencies failed to share information about a ____ terrorist threat.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "authority", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "control (right to control)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war against Iraq is an appropriate ____ to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Alumni have expressed much positive reaction to the Alumni Association's recent initiatives to ____ its use of electronic newsletters and its Web site.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The trial court noted that the newspaper articles ____ reported events and provided no editorial comment.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you want to improve in English, I recommend that you read ____ of books for pleasure.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "attitude", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government will never win the battle ____ drug-taking.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Entrants in this competition are challenged to use or ____ the building's unique infrastructure in the service of the people who learn and teach here.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Using a computer program makes it easier to ____ long pieces of writing.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people think it was no ____ that there was a terror alarm two days before the election.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Her efforts have continued to ____ in the last few months. I think she may be having problems at home.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "How the ____ changed when he entered a room: it was warm, electric, somehow bigger.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "controversy", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The best ____ in learning a new language is to find a girlfriend or boyfriend who speaks it!", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If he is correct this would certainly be an elementary solution to an ____ problem.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The role of doctors as a conscience of the community deserves more consideration in times of stress and under difficult ____ such as war.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Unfortunately, many drug users ____ from prison only to find themselves back there a few months later. This is because they cannot find or keep a job, and need to steal to finance their drug-taking habits.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A student whose total absences in a course, excused or unexcused, ____ ten per trimester is liable to fail the course.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students need to ____ with the department offering the master's degree to ensure the correct credential courses are taken.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In this section of the course, we cover less familiar territory, ____ the equations of relativistic acceleration.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "From the quality of the writing I can only ____ that someone helped him. His work is usually nowhere near as good.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "At weddings the speeches usually ____ the food.", "Opt_1": "appear", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As a result of the rise in the price of oil, the government has decided not to ____ the proposed tax increase.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you do not ____ the rules of the classroom, you will be sent to the headmaster.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We will not ____ unless some of you not only believe in the Constitution, but are willing to engage in public service.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She had shown no ____ to engage in abusive conduct.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "commodity", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "a product; something you can buy"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When you ____ a primary source, you are undertaking the most important job of the historian.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people ____ pictures to the emails they send.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "manifest", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "show"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some people think it was no ____ that there was a terror alarm two days before the election.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Remember that more than one factor may be the cause of a problem and that symptoms may often ____ in their appearance.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "overlap", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some animals, such as the tortoise or snail, have an external shell ____ than an internal skeleton.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is a ____ to think that you can put off working until the week before the exam and still pass it.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is evidence that increases in short sale transactions ____ stock price declines.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Advertising marketed directly to the consumer may minimize the risks and ____ the benefits of medications.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Psychologist Peter Wason discovered that we have enormous difficulty understanding certain sentences that ____ common sense.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The most important ____ of the new design is that it consumes less power.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you ____ the globe by 360\ufffdX, you will return to your starting point.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "rotate", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To include an image on your website, you will need to ____ the image into your webpage using an HTML editor.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Politics is still a ____ male profession.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ version of our anatomy information system has evolved from several previous systems.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "While its ____ of clarity was seen by some early critics as a clear symptom of error and confusion, it was seen by others as a hallmark of genius.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ is to find the right mixture of materials that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If mobile phones ____ any further, the keys will be too small to use.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "cancel", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to cut or stop from happening"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Twins born from the same egg are called ____ twins. They look exactly the same. Fraternal twins look a little different from each other.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All students whose college/university will be forwarding tuition payments will need to contact the OSA to find out the ____ procedure.", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you do not ____ the rules of the classroom, you will be sent to the headmaster.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In many cases what was once an ____ is now taken for granted. Remarkable inventions, once assimilated into daily life, become routine.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will need to ____ your situation as clearly as possible and provide appropriate supporting documentation.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "How can I restrict ____ to my Web pages?", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school took the students on a visit to the history museum to see a special exhibition of Roman ____ equipment.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ student at our school spends about 90 minutes doing homework every evening.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "average", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "ordinary, typical"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Politics is still a ____ male profession.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A ____ error in editing is to fix a word or phrase at one part of a sentence and not see that the fix affected something else in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Volleyball players must ____ in order, and every player must do this (i.e. a team may NOT have a designated setter/hitter/etc. who does not ____ out).", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "rotate", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Wikipedia is a wonderful ____ for high school students, but the information it contains must be checked for reliability.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Medical science now uses a computer scanning ____ to examine the interior of the human body.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The patient is making ____ progress after the 5-hour operation.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Due to her student teaching commitments Murray was unable to ____ this year's event.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of young men who walk around with large aggressive dogs is that they are from the working class and are criminals.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The teaching profession is usually not attractive to those who are still pupils themselves. This choice of ____ is normally made much later.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was not a ____ that anybody in the world would consider wise.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to communicate in a way ____ words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Computer scan technology can enhance the ____ of many sports injuries.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The proposal will not deprive students of the ____ protections to which they are entitled.", "Opt_1": "tough", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The elders in the village are fighting to ____ their people's traditions, but the younger ones want to join the modern world of computers and mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Since most employers spend less than a minute scanning a resume, it is necessary to be brief and to ____ all that is important.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "What skills did you ____ in the process of completing your course?", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "attain", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Those who could not transform, chose not to, or who were considered a threat to the ____ were imprisoned and eliminated.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The new factory near the school will ____ parts for mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The last ____ of the flooded village was evacuated by a helicopter.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Board provided an inadequate ____ of reasons for its 1981 decision.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is especially true from an investing perspective when repeating the same strategy could be a road to ____ disaster.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The final ____ of rebuilding the school will be finished by the end of the vacation.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He has only loose ____ of basic verb grammar. He quite often chooses the wrong tense or forgets the -s ending.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is a direct ____ of how the black hole deforms space and time, a four-dimensional concept that Einstein called spacetime.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I am no expert in animal behavior, but anyone with even a slight knowledge of the ____ must be impressed with their complex forms of social behavior.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The proposal will not deprive students of the ____ protections to which they are entitled.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The students began to ____ when their teacher told them they would have a test on the last day before Christmas.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "King Charles not only lost the opportunity to establish an ____ kingdom; he also lost his life.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You can ____ of old batteries in the container outside the cafeteria.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The two departments have failed to ____ and coordinate their efforts in implementing the laws and regulations on the use of wetland areas.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The committee was asked to ____ a report listing the reasons in favour of invading Iraq.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that growth and globalization also threaten to ____ environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is research that could ____ help in the treatment of certain kinds of cancer.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The teacher gave me a ____ about the need to be in class on time with all my materials.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In most companies you have to have a high ____ before you are entitled to a company car.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "service", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to ____ an extension with the TA regarding such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer simply a health problem - it is a symptom of a greater cultural ____ that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "For reasons that are not yet completely clear, practice and theory usually ____ at this point.", "Opt_1": "retain", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school has a ratio of ____ one teacher for every fifteen students.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of happiness will not go on increasing in anything near the same proportion as the ____ of wealth.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If we ____ that the dimension of a hydrogen atom is about 0.2 nm, then the corresponding confinement energy is about 38 eV.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government ____ produced a wide range of responses.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The number of students in the school will ____ to multiply in the next few years as Frankfurt increases in popularity.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A ____ driving license does not entitle the license holder to drive a bus or a truck.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Check the ____ below for specific dates and starting times.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She chose to reject the ____ that there is an increased risk of having a second child with the same disorder.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "diagnosis", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is only one error in your writing. You put: He play tennis ____ of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There will be a ____ class after school today for those who want extra practice for the test.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We should avoid the error of assuming that we will ever be able to ____ the causes of his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Among male baboons, dominance ____ is independent of maternal ____, and changes markedly with age; males reach their highest ____ between 8 and 10 years of age.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer simply a health problem - it is a symptom of a greater cultural ____ that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, ____ not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ of the government's willingness to pay kidnappers to release hostages is that now there are more kidnappings and more hostages.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most companies ____ to replace machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We southerners, and especially we white southerners, owe a huge ____ to valiant civil rights leaders like Martin Luther King.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ to the school grounds is the stream. You must not cross it.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you want to ____ the chess club, please sign your name on the list below.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you can ____ your intelligence with hard work, you have a good chance of success.", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "reinforce", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "All political parties must ____ in their proposals to stamp out racism.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Using a new technique to trap and ____ single particles with lasers, an international group of researchers have demonstrated that Brownian motion of a single particle behaves differently than Einstein theorized one century ago.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "frustrate", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He is an American citizen which obviously puts him in a different ____ from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The number of ____ warm nights and the length of heat waves will increase significantly over nearly all land areas across the globe.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The main ____ of the greater study, of which this paper is a part, is to develop a model of discursive exclusion of groups of people in the public sphere.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is ____ to consider her difficulties at school in the context of her chaotic home life.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The demand for oil is likely to ____ as people in developing countries such as China and India acquire cars.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In this assignment, you will need to ____ an array of numbers, so that your computer code executes correctly.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of the school behind the car park is for seniors only.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government had to retreat from its starting position in the face of ____ criticism in the newspapers.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Board may presume that those actions created a hostile or abusive work ____ which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If there is any question whether the individual might have a physical problem, the mental health professional should ____ a complete examination.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We must find a way to ____ the new questioning skills along with the new curriculum when the funding is gone.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ way of attacking the security of computer programs is to feed them unexpected and deceptive inputs.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This alone makes the book a worthwhile read for students whose received knowledge about Africans is often little more than a ____ of passive victims.", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school is likely to lose students if the government goes ahead with its proposed ____ to reduce tax benefits for parents.", "Opt_1": "plenty", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A primary function of the system is to ____ the sharing of information with others.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is often necessary to associate a complex set of \"metadata\" with each data ____ in order to make that datum useful.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is not easy to represent an abstract idea in picture ____ so that ESL students can understand it.", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school is looking for students who would like to do voluntary work at the ____ old people's home.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is common knowledge that credit cards are a temporary solution that can snowball into a ____ problem.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ minister has decided to cancel the planned visit to Batavia in view of the outbreak of war in the country.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All the ESL student's teachers can ____ influence the speed at which he or she learns English.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Illegal drugs are grouped into one or other ____ according to how dangerous they are considered.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Over the same period research was unable to ____ significant effects on achievement from readily available school characteristics.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The explanation for this ____ decision lies in the immediate circumstances surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The system uses a ____ inference engine that does not require users to explicitly provide information about the start or ending points of their journeys.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ answer is not at all straightforward, unless the uncertainty itself is related in a particular way to the passage of time.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "But the mice did not undergo ____ cognitive testing, which requires intact mobility to navigate various mazes.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Although Katrina affected the material environment of Louisiana, it did not ____ the great spirit of the people here.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "What steps do I take to draw a random ____ of a target audience in my county to do a needs assessment or gather baseline data?", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If we are to contemplate actions designed to reverse the ____ of current difficulties in Viet Nam we ought to lay the groundwork.", "Opt_1": "pattern", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Close to 30% of students did not perceive it to be cheating to lie to an instructor about having an illness or some other emergency in order to ____ a work deadline.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To develop a ____ approach to business, managers must utilize the strengths of their employees in assigning tasks.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "massive", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If someone invites you to their party, it's polite to send them a ____ and tell them if you can come or not.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This ____ examines attitudes regarding the campus-area housing market.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The volume of business between Europe and Asia has ____ increased in recent years.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Too much ____ can trigger problems with mental and physical health, particularly over a prolonged period of time.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I am no ____ in animal behavior, but anyone with even a slight knowledge of the field must be impressed with their complex forms of social behavior.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "With her good grades she is now getting the ____ of all her hard work.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you want to know whether an ____ is common or not, look it up in Google.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We got some very ____ results in our science experiment. I think the thermometer was not working correctly.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You must write a ____ of 3 pages for your final report.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The remaining 40 percent said that they were not ____ with the term 'sustainable agriculture'.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "familiar", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Latin alphabet did not ____ between the vowel and consonant sounds of i and u.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has succeeded in reducing unemployment ____ older people; conversely, young people are having ever more difficulty finding a job.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most governments refuse to ____ with kidnappers.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "University ____ will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages instead of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ farmers who grow crops that can be used to run cars.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Even today some Russian people refuse to ____ Stalin with the terrible crimes that were committed when he was Russian leader.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "cancel", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is a very ____ and inadequate outline of a few of the leading points in a very large investigation with which I am occupied.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This international degree course has been especially created for international students in their final ____ of studies in Law.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was difficult for the two sides in the dispute to find a ____ time to meet.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ its lunchtime sports program after hearing a request from the student council.", "Opt_1": "consent", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to agree", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "But it is not a substitute for ____ food safety programs throughout the food distribution system.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government ____ produced a wide range of responses.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a ____ implication on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Bailey decided to ____ the problem head-on by scheduling an open public meeting.", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "During its congress, Committee failed to ____ even one woman to a leading position.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You can ____ all the things you need for class at the school's bookstore.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A significant ____ of winning the bid for the next Olympic Games is that it will cost the country an enormous amount of money.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Unlike other animals, humans have no ____ for survival; we often choose to do things that may be detrimental to our health.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some institutions did not ____ these issues because they predicted them and dealt with them in advance.", "Opt_1": "form", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We used this information to ____ a continuous measure of the ratio of subject-specific coursework to total coursework.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Committee is concerned that children dropping out of school during the compulsory ____ of education have insufficient alternative educational opportunities.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The number of students in the school will continue to ____ in the next few years as Frankfurt increases in popularity.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Exam question: Distinguish between the ____ of the iris and the ____ of the cornea.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The western end of the trade ____ appears to have developed earlier than the eastern end, principally because of the development of the empires in the west.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "route", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There are ____ students from Korea at Frankfurt International School.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This program will ____ entry to the field and to advanced study of nutrition.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For the purposes of this study, then, increasing the testing strength did not ____ more accurate results.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "yield", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to produce", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Teachers and parents can learn and share ideas for helping to work for more successful outcomes in the ____ from school to adult life.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We held that the entry was illegal because police failed to ____ their purpose before using the crowbar to pry the door open.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "compel", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Please ____ your feet from the table! People have to eat here!", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "cancel", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will not get a ____ reply to your email. He is very busy at the moment.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has set a clear limit on how much pollution factories are allowed to release into the ____ every year.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "issue", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As large and difficult as it was, it was not the ____ problem. The deeper problem was conceptual.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You ____ yourself to unnecessary danger if you drive a car without wearing a seat belt.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government shows little ____ into the reasons why so many young people become addicted to drugs and alcohol.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most people who use a wheelchair or mobility devices do not ____ them as confining. They are viewed as liberating; a means of getting around.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Mrs Cho spoke on ____ of the Korean Parents Group and thanked the school for buying Korean books for the library.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In most countries of the world you need to get a ____ before you can drive a car.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students are able to use basic communication and mathematics skills for purposes and situations they will ____ throughout their lives.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "encounter", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Further analysis suggested that the ____ was worse for women than men.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company had to ____ their profit predictions after the cost of oil doubled within 6 months.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We must trust the scientists and experts to make the right decisions to ____ the environment.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This document will explain some of the problems that could exist because the computer is unable to ____ updates for Windows Vista.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In my opinion the government's ____ for banning smoking is very weak. Surely they don't expect people to agree!", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The opening of the new sports ____ was the biggest operation in the school's history.", "Opt_1": "block", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The elders in the village are fighting to retain their people's traditions, but the younger ones want to ____ the modern world of computers and mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The minister gave an ____ answer when asked if the government intended to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Nevertheless, thirty-three years later, Israel is not willing to ____ from the Golan Heights to the 4 June 1967, prewar border.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I do not feel that the possible applications of a line of research should be allowed to ____ the directions of research in my laboratory.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This tells us that there is a very large market for us to expand into, if we take ____ of the opportunities as they arise.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The equator is an ____ line that divides the earth into a northern and southern hemisphere.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Don't forget to ____ your research sources at the end of your writing.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We view his behavior as very serious and we hope this ban will serve as an example.If you ____ the rules about downloading internet files, you will not be allowed to use the computer lab.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We had to make sure that our customers in China knew that what we were doing was not an ____ on Chinese industry, but a dispute over a legitimate issue.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is ____ impossible to do well in school unless you are a good reader.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Trying to water-ski for the first time is difficult but if you keep practising, you will ____ learn how to do it.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Almost everyone believes that terrorism should be fought, but there is little agreement about the ____ in which it should be done.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has made ____ progress towards its goal of reducing child poverty.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You will ____ your chances of success if you are absent from school so often.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Using computer modeling, he was able to ____ the relationship between the strength of a stellar wind and the age of a star.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "People have been trying for decades or maybe even centuries in an attempt to bring this ____ problem to an end.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Why, Graeme Newman asks, has reform after reform failed to halt the ____ of crime?", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "spread", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We wanted to establish a long-term ____ that could grow with our company.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The text should ____ a concise description of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company's target for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to ____ this figure by 40%.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many students ____ their chances of examination success because they only start to work hard a few weeks before.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "consume", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to use, or use up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You need to ____ your work a little more closely for silly spelling or punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot attach its ____ meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government was fully ____ of the magnitude of its decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you currently do not possess the ____ to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is easy to use the internet to ____ a lot of information. Whether it is of good quality is a different matter!", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Her family were persecuted by the Nazis, so it's no surprise that she shows ____ against the Germans.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please ____ me a seat at the back of the school bus.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a ____ way to obtain energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Very few students are allowed to ____ the course, and permission is by petition only.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has done a deal with the nurses union in order to ____ strikes in hospitals.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Not everyone knows that Texas was once a ____ of Mexico.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school decided to ____ when the angry parent said that he would contact his lawyer.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We can separate white light into its component colors with a prism and use an ____ prism to recombine the light.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school needs to ____ the students' project work to the examination board before the end of the month.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you want to ____ in school you will have to study hard!", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many students who receive a grade lower than they want, do so because they fail to ____ their texts.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "attend", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We should never ____ or blame any person on account of outward actions that are common to all; but only on account of their principles.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "That doesn't mean I have a personality disorder because I ____ myself in a different manner to different people.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "An employee is entitled to no ____ for the first seven calendar days of disability unless the disability continues for more than 21 days.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The political system must not be allowed to degenerate into unlimited ____ rule, which could result in the erosion of individual liberty.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "By running these ads, the newspaper is sending the message that it considers this a ____ product to sell.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "While I don't present this as ____ the ultimate method that everyone should use, it is important that a standardized technique be adopted.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Rumours about teachers ____ quickly through schools.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is important to ____ that the information noted on the sign-off form is correct and that all necessary signatures have been obtained.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you ____ the figures carefully, you will see some strong patterns.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Aschoff's trip failed because he was unable to defend his ____ against the competitive approach favored by German and Russian scientists.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Incoming personal mail and packages are not ____ to university business and are not permitted.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police had difficulty in trying to ____ the enormous crowd after the pop concert.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There are ____ 100 days until your final examination. It's time you started working.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is too early to make an ____ diagnosis of her problems in learning English.", "Opt_1": "related", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This finding may explain why increasing numbers of people in the United States lack the natural ability to ____ food intake and body weight.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "realize", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We recognize that ____ beyond a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students must ____ that at least one of the three courses they take to satisfy the general and school cores is a Humanities course.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Administrators and supervisors are expected to see that those who report to them are informed about, understand and ____ with regulations.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot attach its ____ meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "rare", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "unusual", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students with Advanced Placement scores of 4 or 5 in English Language ____ a credit toward graduation but not toward the English major.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The most important ____ for selecting a research topic is that you are really interested in it!", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government should not ____ young unmarried mothers by giving them free housing.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is now clear to me that they shared an ____ inability to view themselves objectively and critically.", "Opt_1": "steady", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a ____ approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Financial aid is the term we use to describe a variety of funds available to help students and their families ____ the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "On the ship, every ____ room and corner was turned into dormitory space; cots were set up to accommodate the overflow.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a familiar symbol of ____ to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government failed to ____ its goal of reducing unemployment among young people.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "accomplish", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The fact that she doesn't speak English did much to ____ the situation.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "complicate", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Individuals are granted the use of the ____ on this website without written permission provided that all of the following conditions are met.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some countries, such as Switzerland, remained ____ in the last world war.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Why have these countries failed to develop ____ receiving billions of dollars in assistance?", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The university advises female students to follow their instinct whether it is safe to ____ a ride home from a man they have just met.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "China has experienced dynamic ____ in the last few years.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In response to these events, this study was initiated to define and investigate the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many birds ____ south in the winter to find warmer temperatures.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "migrate", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Progress is so fast these days that some technological products become ____ within a very short time.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "UK airports have increased the ____ of security staff since the terrorist attacks in London.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many large companies employ people to analyze a ____ such as the way people spend their money on holiday, etc.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally rigid bodies undergo multiple, concurrent, ____ frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Our teachers ____ the school's philosophy that only excellence is good enough.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "His current measurement results are not precise enough to ____ exactly the minimum that the ball is sitting in.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most companies guarantee to ____ machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Now that you have revised your work, the next ____ of the writing process is to edit it for errors of grammar or spelling.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "For your child to be considered your dependent, you must ____ more than half of their support.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A student seeking a career in this ____ of study will have abundant opportunities to develop personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is feared that disagreement about what to do in Iraq will damage the ____ between the USA and the UK.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "People with another genetic variant, glycine (Gly-389), had no ____ to the drug compared to the placebo.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "response", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The idea that there is ____ in nature is part of most world views.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people think that the government's proposals to reduce teenage crime are ____ and will not work.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He told reporters that he did not want to ____ in the dispute over the prime minister.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to ____ a full application including: cover sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We view his behavior as very serious and we hope this ban will serve as an example.If you ____ the rules about downloading internet files, you will not be allowed to use the computer lab.", "Opt_1": "violate", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "create", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is fair to praise the government for their successful efforts to reduce unemployment ____ older people.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is advisable that you put your name on these waiting lists ____ to your arrival.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I don't have very much knowledge in the ____ of electronics.", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The new teacher has been away quite often this year. I ____ that she will not be given a permanent job at the school.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "speculate", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Teachers ____ to get annoyed if students do not pay attention in class.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "expel", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to drive or push out"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many students look for ____ work between leaving school and starting university.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Elders says that the U.S. must ____ its sick health care system.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "depend", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "reform", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company is investigating ____ of increasing its business in Asia and Africa.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In Ancient Rome not every ____ had equal rights.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It's no surprise that she is so quiet in class. She can ____ speak a word of English.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She needed to earn enough money to be able to ____ London's sky-high prices.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "manifest", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "show"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "During this course you will ____ your knowledge of German, by focusing on the four language skills, namely speaking, listening, reading and writing.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's no surprise that she is so quiet in class. She can ____ speak a word of English.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is virtually impossible to predict which infants in the latter group will not ____ without support.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Employees interested in participating in a ____ tax sheltered annuity program should contact their personnel officer.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Instead of quick results, Cronbach (1963) believed that consistent experiences gradually improve ____ over time.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Computer viruses ____ themselves to documents such as word processing files and spreadsheets.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You need to know a little more about the ____ before you criticize the government's decision.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students successfully completing a family history ____ should demonstrate a significant range of skills and abilities in research and critical thinking.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A three-year Indian bachelor's degree is NOT ____ to a U.S. bachelor's degree.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Hopes continue to ____ that a peace treaty can be negotiated.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to negotiate an extension with the TA ____ such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "below"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Furthermore, the system can also measure environmental conditions in the ____ surroundings including ambient light level, humidity, and temperature.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If a person tends to be cautious in relationships or at work, it is ____ that her investment decisions will also be cautious.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Do you ever feel like some Asian traditions ____ the need for communication or being able to freely display your emotions?", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many more people ____ a house in England than in Germany.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government's ____ in his second term of office is to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "On your first day in a new school it is difficult to ____ all the information that you are given.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She came to school yesterday ____ feeling very unwell.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is not an infinite ____ of oil and natural gas.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is very little difference in the quality of learning received by distance education students and ____ students, according to a study.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was perhaps the most significant function of ____ and local governments.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "King Charles not only lost the opportunity to establish an ____ kingdom; he also lost his life.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors ____ that people eat 5 fruits or vegetables every day.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The political system must not be allowed to ____ into unlimited majority rule, which could result in the erosion of individual liberty.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The top ____ of this car is 230kph.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Typical conversations ____ a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans accumulate as they grow.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Catherwood Library is the most comprehensive ____ of its type in North America.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As migration is a spatial ____ process, it is important to comprehend how migrants perceive space and choose a destination in the space.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You need to assimilate the material covered by the homework problems in ____ to pass the quizzes and final examination.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a serious ____ of workers in the profession of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The student is experiencing ____ difficulties with the reading requirements of the course.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She thinks that the homeless children probably will ____ more poorly, educationally, than the children who come from homes.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "While you may not admit to ____ pressure, you must be aware of its almost constant presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Our committee was asked to make recommendations to reduce the ____ between teachers, parents and students, and improve the three-way partnership.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Tour de France is an ____ bike race that is watched by millions of people on the roads and on TV.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ was first observed in 1911 by Onnes, who noted that the resistance of a frozen mercury rod abruptly dropped to zero.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore apart a nation and created many social problems that did not ____ before its invention.", "Opt_1": "regret", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In a world of ____ problems but finite resources, competition for adequate attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the ____ did not acknowledge the positive developments in the industry since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "form"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Department Coordinator, elected by peers, has the same one vote as the others and has no ____ over her peers.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We have never in history needed to ____ of so much waste as we do today.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Developments in computer technology may ____ make accurate weather forecasting possible.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The student was ____ active with the experiment and did not attempt to contribute.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The new government plans to ____ the best possible health service for all of its citizens.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "attend", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Lack of financial aid is a significant ____ on the chances of success in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Why are most intellectuals and education theorists so ____ to allowing ordinary parents to choose which school their children will attend?", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some steps you can take to ____ yourself and your property are: Lock your room when sleeping and when you leave your room.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We can only ____ that Fulton was already too deeply committed to his own plan to consider alternative ideas.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I experienced her as a very ____ teacher who had empathy for her students.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many German companies have decided to ____ their factories to parts of the world where workers are cheaper.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "transfer", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The many hours of practice that usually underlie exceptional ____ remain out of sight to the casual observer.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Her ____ skills are very good; she has much more difficulty with calculation.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "verbal", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students choosing this option must select a faculty adviser from the departmental faculty who will ____ the student's program.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You must ____ a bibliography to all reports that are based on information found in books or on the internet.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some animals, such as the tortoise or snail, have an ____ shell rather than an internal skeleton.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Teachers did not ____ because of students behaving badly but rather because student behavior was not adequately managed.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "migrate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government is planning to make a ____ tomorrow morning on its discussions the doctors' union.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There are very few people living today who were born ____ to the first world war.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The producer of these webpages has long been an ____ of the value of computers in language teaching.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government is thinking of passing a law that will ____ all house owners to exchange their oil heating system for one that runs on gas.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "With winter weather comes the need to ____ your home, automobile and family to deal with the colder temperatures.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ failed to persuade workers themselves to consider domestic service as anything other than a temporary transition.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most people who use a wheelchair or mobility devices do not ____ them as confining. They are viewed as liberating; a means of getting around.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "complicate", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If your students are not at the ____ you have planned for them in the middle of the quarter, you will need to investigate why this is so.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has made overall progress towards its ____ of reducing child poverty.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The issue is of a ____ that cannot be solved by the school alone.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There was also no ____ record of an attempt to measure the relationship between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has announced ____ plans to reduce long-term unemployment.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A group of artists who were working and teaching in the Boston area had a ____ idea: to create a new kind of school for professional education in the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I am an American clergywoman with the unusual ____ of teaching these young people the Hebrew language, in Arabic.", "Opt_1": "assignment", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "assignment", "Opt_1_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Because of their mobile lifestyle, they did not ____ many objects.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A regular driving ____ does not entitle the ____ holder to drive a bus or a truck.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to enable him to make a ____ decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The parents decided to ____ against the school's expulsion their son.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A ____ example of ambiguity is the sentence: \"I do not like visiting aunts.\"", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to promote the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are ____ it!", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Plagiarism is easy to ____ but often hard to define. This is partly because the legal rules differ sharply from the ethical ones.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company won the contract to ____ the government with 30,000 special computers for primary schools.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not in the best interests of children if their parents are ____ protective of them.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Testing personnel will not ____ any tester who is cheating, but will complete the Testing Incident Report and submit to the supervisor.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I'm sorry, but I will ____ not be able to come to the meeting next week.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "So if they go extinct on one tropical mountain there is only a slight chance that they will recolonize from a ____ nearby mountain.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The PBL ____ is rather time-consuming and requires the teacher to invest a lot of effort over an extended period of time.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The father stated he was from the neighbourhood of Bandon, where he had been unable to ____ any employment.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's ____ is, also advises man on woman's potential and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A typical problem is that many companies will only employ workers with ____, but how do young people gain that ____ if they are not given a job? This is called a \"vicious circle\".", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most western countries want to ____ with China. It's the largest market in the world and its developing fast.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The tax system must not discourage economic activity and it must not ____ from the tax systems in other countries.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Because multicultural audiences will likely become more and more common, you will need to ____ cultural differences when you analyze your audience.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The water ____ is one of the natural processes that are familiar to most students.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school is not a business. Its ____ is not to make a large profit, but to earn enough money to provide the best possible education.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My overall impression is that this plan describes a very ____ attempt to address an important issue in a scientifically credible manner.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "ambitious", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you want to run this software, you will need to ____ the operating system.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government shows little ____ into the reasons why so many young people become addicted to drugs and alcohol.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The police were not ____ of controlling the street demonstrations. They had to call in the army.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She is yet to master basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. ____ of He does ...", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When parents decide to send their children to a ____ -paying school, education becomes a commodity.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Which activity are you going to ____ next time? - I think I'll try chess.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge ____ regarding the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students who have problems at home often seek the ____ of a trusted teacher at school.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The director was not prepared to even listen to ideas ____ to his own.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He was expelled from school for a ____ attempt to cheat in the end of year exams.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is an artificial example to ____ how the method works. In real data, the sequences are much longer, and there's no mistaking a match.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He also showed conclusively that this was not a ____ procedure for patients suffering from depression or anxiety.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The University of California library system faces a ____ in relation to the costs of online journal subscriptions.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ for writing such a report consists of the following steps: Choosing a subject; Finding sources of materials; Gathering the notes, etc.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She was unable to transfer her ability and ____ to this new problem.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A ____ and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too vague or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people think that the ____ way to stop people smoking is to raise the price of cigarettes sky-high.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "anonymous", "Opt_3": "ideal", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "ideal", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_3_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In this assignment, you will need to manipulate an array of numbers, so that your computer ____ executes correctly.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "My ESL teacher has the ____ to talk about his own school days.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Board of Trustees met in April 2006 to discuss this report, and decided to ____ the construction of a 500 kW turbine.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Picasso's ____ to draw found expression in a variety of forms.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There seemed to be no ____ of coping with the war debts that were overwhelming both nation and states.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I ____ that problems at home are the reason for her poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is a very ____ and inadequate outline of a few of the leading points in a very large investigation with which I am occupied.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Only time will ____ the debate about whether the earth really is warming up or not.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is an activity in which I expect you to work together. Do not try to ____ with each other.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We often hear that now is the period of the most ____ change. From one perspective, this might be correct.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government did not ____ with the recommendations regarding the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Including future irrelevant costs generally will not lead to a poor choice; it will only ____ the analysis.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was not wise to use the river as the ____ for your drinking water before you analyzed it.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is surprising what you can ____ if you make an effort.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "accomplish", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to do or achieve"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Storage of personal information not related to university business must be limited and must not ____ in any way with the storage and maintenance of university data.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is now clear to me that they shared an ____ inability to view themselves objectively and critically.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An orange pencil is not a suitable ____ to do your homework with.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some assignments will be graded; others will ____ receive a check-mark.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My parents will ____ that I did this work without help.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The writer Emile Zola exposed the affair to the general ____ in the literary newspaper L'Aurore (The Dawn) in a famous open letter to the President.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}]]